# **Ali ISMAIL**



### **Contact**

#### Address:

Tartus - Syria

#### Phone:

+963 934163403

#### **Email:**

alihismail2911997@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

## Languages

Arabic – Native Language English – Professional Working Proficiency

### **Hobbies**

- Traveling
- Cooking
- Swimming
- Playing music

## **Summary**

I am a frontend developer with very good experience as I worked with a website development company in Syria <u>Akitu</u> <u>Dynamic</u> as a Frontend developer.

Where I became an expert in designing and modifying blogger templates (Google) and gained a great expert in CSS, HTML and JavaScript.

I started learning and working in PHP language within the framework of Laravel's work and gained good experience in it. I learned to search for solutions to programming problems and learned logical analysis in order to find the solution.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Able to work under pressure within a team work
- Strong decision maker
- Problem solver
- Electronic circuit analysis
- Arduino programming

## **Experience**

German Arabic translator assistant – 04/2016 Until now

Kamel Ismail (licensed translator)

**Computer and network maintenance technician** – 05/2018 to 09/2019

- OBKO online gaming center Latakia
- Web Developer 10/2019 to 06/2021
  - Akitu Dynamic (Front end developer).

### **Education**

Bachelor's degree in Communications and Electronics Engineering - Tishreen University – Latakia (2021)

### **Certifications**

Programming Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, PHP OOP, CSS, SQL, MySQL, java, Python, C++.